<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inertry</title>
    <link>https://blog.inertry.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Inertry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 13:18:45 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://blog.inertry.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Change text color in Sticky notes window - Synapbook</title>
      <link>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-05-15-change-text-color-in-sticky-notes-window-synapbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 04:27:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-05-15-change-text-color-in-sticky-notes-window-synapbook/</guid>
      <description>There are two ways to change the text color in the SynapBook sticky notes window:
1. Using the keyboard Move to the line you want to change and press the Change Color key.
Blue - ctrl + alt + b
Red - ctrl + alt + r
* Press this key again to change to default color (black).
 Using the mouse Move to the line you want to change and press the right mouse button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insert checkbox into sticky notes window - Synapbook</title>
      <link>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-05-14-insert-checkbox-into-sticky-notes-window-synapbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 04:25:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-05-14-insert-checkbox-into-sticky-notes-window-synapbook/</guid>
      <description>In the SynapBook sticky notes window, there are two ways to check boxes:
1. Using the keyboard Move to the line you want to change and press the checkbox insert shortcuts alt + c.
2. Using the mouse Move to the line you want to change and press the right mouse button. In the toolbar that appears, click the button with the checkbox image.
Thanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Notes for cloud version - Synapbook</title>
      <link>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-04-01-sticky-notes-for-cloud-version-synapbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 04:17:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-04-01-sticky-notes-for-cloud-version-synapbook/</guid>
      <description>If you are using Sticky Notes, which is built into Windows, you can use SynapBook as a sticky notes cloud version.
SynapBook offers almost the same interface as Sticky Notes, but has the following additional benefits:
 All notes are synchronized to the server so they can be accessed from any PC Support font change and highlighter function for checkbox and highlight Supports minimized status with title only Tree structure allows organizing contents  SynapBook is a powerful note management program that supports also Evernote-like notes editing, not only the use of Sticky Notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Google Keep and Evernote Replacement - SynapBook</title>
      <link>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-04-01-the-google-keep-and-evernote-replacement-synapbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 04:08:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-04-01-the-google-keep-and-evernote-replacement-synapbook/</guid>
      <description>If you are using Google Keep or Evernote for organizing notes, you can use SynapBook as an alternative.
SynapBook has the following advantages over Evernote and Google Keep,
Pros.  Organizing contents into a tree structure  Variety of lettering styles  Boxing in groups  Group folding  Separate support for Memo function based on search and Note function for storing separately systematically.  Table of contents supported Powerful hotkeys that can be customized  You can assign hotkeys to almost all functions, and you can customize them to your liking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Keep vs SynapBook - Which Is King of Simple Note Taking?</title>
      <link>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-04-01-google-keep-vs-synapbook-which-is-king-of-simple-note-taking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 03:49:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-04-01-google-keep-vs-synapbook-which-is-king-of-simple-note-taking/</guid>
      <description>Common point  Synchronize data through the server so you can accesss the same memo from anywhere. It supports tags in memo, easy to sort and search for keywords. Image insertion support. Archiving feature allows you to archive what you need to keep for later viewing.  Google Keep Pros.  Web-based access to web pages is available anywhere It is simple and neat. Voice memo can be memorized.  https://keep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V1.2.0 Popup memo released like Windows Sticky Notes</title>
      <link>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-03-19-v1.2.0-popup-memo-released-like-windows-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 22:42:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-03-19-v1.2.0-popup-memo-released-like-windows-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>In SynapBook V1.2 You can edit your notes in a separate window like Windows Sticky Notes app(you can use SynapBook as Sticky Notes cloud version).
Additional Title mode which shows only titlebar is available as well. Popup note feature makes it easy to view and manage your notes. ;-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Evernote and Synapbook</title>
      <link>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-03-03-comparison-of-evernote-and-synapbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 23:57:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-03-03-comparison-of-evernote-and-synapbook/</guid>
      <description>Common features  Cloud Synchronization enables you to access memo contents created by PC and mobile phone anywhere Data is stored locally so that it can be accessed even during fast search and network disconnection Supports sorting and tagging of notes Support for inserting images into notes  Strengths of Evernote versus Synapbook  iOS support Extremely powerful Web scrap functionality Content encryption support It is a stable application that has a long history and many users use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Official Synapbook V1.0 released</title>
      <link>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-02-18-official-synapbook-v1.0-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 04:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.inertry.com/article/2018-02-18-official-synapbook-v1.0-released/</guid>
      <description>Finally upgraded the version to V1.0. We think it would be 8.0 or more so if we update the actual version with hundreds of releases, but we have not been able to upgrade the version since we have been operating in semi-private mode for about 2 years, and we have been beta-tagged like Google because of concerns about unstable There was also intention to operate. ;-)
Now that we have switched to full public release because it&amp;rsquo;s time, we have revised the version to V1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>